( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
Don't worry, dear. Okay?
No one will bother Mikoy anymore.
- Are you sure you're not hurt?
- Nothing.
The one who attacked you
was Jepoy's brother.
And according to him,
he was only avenging his brother.
there's only one thing we can say.
He's setting you up
to become the Moraviano principale.
You will become the leader
of the entire syndicate.
- Do you feel guilty?
- Guilty about what?
About what we're doing to Mikoy.
Because I'm sure if we hadn't
recruited Mikoy for our mission,
maybe by now, he would just be happy
being with Chiara.
He would only be thinking about the love
they share and nurture every day, right?
Is that real happiness?
I want to fully commit to this mission.
I'm ready to help you
bring down the Moravianos.
Mikoy?
Well… He seems happy with his new role.
Your relationship with him
gave us a very good cover
to be here in the Philippines.
getting to know the family
of his new partner.
Just being happy. Just having fun, right?
But I know
there's another reason
why we're here in the Philippines.
This is the perfect place
for our center of Moravianos.
She looks good in that picture.
And if she wanted to, she could
work anywhere she wants.
Do you suspect her?
Is that why her picture is there?
You also can't deny that she has proximity
to the world of the Moravianos
because of her Mommy and Daddy.
we still haven't found
any connection to the syndicate.
You…
What do you think?
Do you think she knows
what her Mommy and Daddy are doing?
You know, Mikoy is useful.
Obviously, that kid
is crazy about you. Right?
Possible. But…
He's not like us.
Why do you say that?
Like, his outlook on life
is very different.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- Thank you for stopping.
Stop.
- Thank you for your help.
- It's okay. No problem.
Are you okay now, ma'am?
It's okay.
Maybe you're starting to be like him.
We have formidable enemies
here in the Philippines.
Papa! If I'm not tough,
then we would all be dead by now.
I'm the reason why we are all still alive.
Let me reassure you
that nothing will stop our plans
here in the Philippines.
La Morte Bianca,
And you don't need to worry
about that anymore.
Mikoy!
We have to work
in a small team just to make sure
that no information will leak
and that our mission
won't get compromised.
He will join you
after he recovers from his setback.
I admit that at first, we framed him.
We blackmailed him
to spy for us on the Moravianos.
Because I realized Agent Alex was right.
More people will become victims
of the syndicate.
More people will get hurt.
More people will be dragged into this.
It's just unfortunate that I was the one
who got pulled into this situation.
But you know,
I've thought about it.
If not me, then who?
If not now,
then when?
Right?
Maybe there's a reason
why I was placed in this situation.
Maybe…
heaven is just giving me
a chance to do the right thing.
Did you use ChatGPT on that?
You definitely didn't write that.
I know you.
What ChatGPT? Hey!
This is not ChatGPT, okay!
Successful? That's easy!
We just need to believe
that we can do this!
As a team. Right?
As Linny, Ming-Ming, and Tuck say…
But you know, Mikoy.
We need something stronger.
Like… a prayer?
You're right!
We need the power of prayer.
We also need prayers,
and that is very important.
But equally important,
we also need to train you.
Train?
We have to make sure
that you can protect yourself.
Because next time,
we might not make it in time
to save your life.
We need to train you,
so you can defend yourself
in even more dangerous situations.
Wait! Hold on!
Why are you here?
Hey you, Angelito.
Why didn't you come over
to your brother's place?
Exactly! We waited for you.
Your mother even cooked.
I suddenly had something
I needed to finish.
By the way, your son is so kind.
Wait. Shall we go now?
Let's go! I'll just change first.
Oh, why does it seem like
you’re making us leave?
Are you hiding something?
Wait a second! Here! Love!
Let’s check this one.
- I thought you brought a girl here.
- Wait! Under the bed!
- That's what I'm saying!
- Really?
- I told you, be careful, love!
- Ouch, ouch.
- Be careful, love!
- It hurts.
- Dad! Mom!
- Let me lean first.
I already told you.
That's not on my mind yet.
Didn't I promise
that I would finish my studies first?
Son, that's right, okay?
Just focus on your studies first.
Because I'm sure
you'll have plenty of time
for girls once you graduate, okay?
And always be well-behaved, okay?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let’s eat first.
Dear, please forgive your father.
Of all people,
you should be the one who understands him.
He's just worried about you.
But when did I let our family down?
And if you ask me,
after everything you need to do
for La Morte Bianca,
I'm just really happy that I met him.
Hi! I am Sofie.
Angelito's friend.
Why are you here, dear?
Did you sleep here?
Are you my son's girlfriend?
Honestly,
We are exploring
whether we are a good match.
Whether we are compatible.
Whether we fit
Oh my, stop right there!
No, but answer me.
Is that what's trendy now?
Is that how it is now?
So there are no more labels.
It's all just a test drive. Like that?
Instead of focusing on labels,
we'd rather focus on each other first.
To get to know each other.
My Angelito?
That's exactly it.
Oh dear!
I don't really care
about labels anyway, okay?
So it's better if we eat
because we brought a lot of food.
- Oh, come on, let's eat.
- I'll excuse myself.
Oh, no, no! Sit down there.
You both sit down. Because honestly,
we need to know
if you're good for our son.
So, sit down. Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Come here. Come here.
You can also treat this like a friend
you can borrow from when necessary.
But just like any friend,
there's a proper way to handle it.
Your turn.
There are four major parts of a gun.
This includes the engine, or the action,
such as bolt-action or semi-automatic.
It’s the heart, or the firing pin.
The barrel where
the bullet passes through.
The only part of a gun
that is connected to you.
You don’t have to change
when you have a gun.
Keep calm.
Just like in normal life,
It’s like a relationship,
And we need to move on
until you hit the right mark.
Do not use it to threaten
or attack anyone.
You should never use
your friend for something bad.
It's only been a few days,
and he's already so good at using a gun.
It's like… he's even better
than movie actors.
The lead movie actor who just does
a montage, a few scenes,
then suddenly they're already good
at handling a gun
or use any weapon. Right?
Just walking down the stairs
and suddenly it's an ultimate makeover.
Exactly! Exactly!
I'll admit he's a quick learner
when it comes to weaponry.
But he still has a lot to learn.
Nice, huh? Wait a second.
I thought we’d do shooting today?
What's this?
I think your knowledge of shooting
is enough.
This time, self-defense.
Self-defense? No offense, okay?
As long as I have a gun,
I don't need to learn karate.
I’m not trying to brag,
but if anyone tries to violate me,
all I can say is…
"You're just one bullet."
But you should not rely on a gun
in every situation.
What if you don't have time
to bring your weapon?
That hurts! Wait! What was that for?
That's the problem with close combat.
You won't have time to draw your gun.
And more likely,
you'll already be down
before you can even move.
Okay, fine! Got it!
That really hurt.
But you know, you're right.
I really should always be ready.
Because you know why I wasn't ready?
Because this can happen.
Because look, this can happen.
So, you're really right.
Right?
You were right.
Nice, right?
You really learn fast.
I really do learn fast.
What are you doing?
What do you mean, what am I doing?
Do you want me to say it?
First,
you enter my room without permission.
You sleep on my bed.
And now, you’re telling my mom and dad
that we’re in a relationship?
Correction. I never claimed
that we’re in a relationship.
As a matter of fact,
what I said was, we have no label.
Even so!
You shouldn’t just barge
into my life without permission.
I don’t know how you get into my room.
So, please, stop invading my privacy!
You know what?
If you were decent,
you’d know it’s not right
to sleep around with just anyone.
You don’t even look homeless.
If this is just some fun for you,
please…
don’t drag me into it. Please.
So, don’t add to it.
Please.
Bok?
- Are you okay?
- Hey! Don’t scare me like that!
Why? Did I say something wrong?
I just asked if you were okay.
What do you need? Why are you here?
So, I asked Rafa where you were.
You said you had
a self-defense session with our asset.
So I came here.
Why?
He has a new lead on our case.
Just follow, okay?
Gosh.
Hey!
Chiara.
Do you know how long I waited?
I kept calling you,
but you weren’t answering.
You know,
I hope you can make time
for the two of us.
It was better when we were in Prague.
At least there, I had you to myself.
Now?
You’re like an OFW.
I barely see you. I can’t even find you.
You’re right. I’ve just
been overwhelmed with work.
But…
I’ll make it up to you.
Make it up?
How will you make it up?
Do you have chocolates?
Or even flowers?
You know, one of my ex-boyfriends,
Just to make it up to me.
Another ex-boyfriend of mine,
he hired Bruno Mars to serenade me.
How will Mr. Pinagpala make it up to me?
Well, he loves her.
Why did he leave her at the altar?
I thought they were going
to stand by their love.
It's because Matteo is threatening him.
If they continue the wedding,
then the man she loves would be killed.
Sir. I’m sorry. I’ve been
looking for Agent Alex.
I called you here
because I want to introduce
someone to you.
Let’s just meet tomorrow.
He is the leader
of the local syndicate
called Sinigang Cartel.
so when the Moravianos
arrived in the country,
Moravianos on the one hand,
Sinigang Cartel on the other one.